<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kun Xie</title>
    <link>https://cskxie.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kun Xie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 21:48:57 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cskxie.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2018</title>
      <link>https://cskxie.github.io/papers/2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 21:48:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cskxie.github.io/papers/2018/</guid>
      <description>[1].Kun Xie, Lele Wang, Xin Wang, Gaogang Xie, Jigang Wen, Guangxing Zhang, Jiannong Cao, Dafang Zhang, Accurate Recovery of Internet Traffic Data: A Sequential Tensor Completion Approach, IEEE/ACM Transactions on Networking, DOI (identifier) 10.1109/TNET.2018.2797094, (CCF A，SCI二区)
[2].Kun Xie, Can Peng, Xin Wang, Gaogang Xie, Jigang Wen, Jiannong Cao, Dafang Zhang, Zheng Qin, Accurate Recovery of Internet Traffic Data Under Variable Rate Measurements, IEEE/ACM Transactions on Networking, accept, (CCF A，SCI二区)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017</title>
      <link>https://cskxie.github.io/papers/2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 21:48:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cskxie.github.io/papers/2017/</guid>
      <description>[9].Kun Xie, Can Peng, Xin Wang, Gaogang Xie, Jigang Wen, Accurate Recovery of Internet Traffic Data Under Dynamic Measurements, INFOCOM 2017 (CCF A, acceptance rate of 20.93%)
[10].Gaogang Xie, Kun Xie, Jun Huang, Xin Wang, Yuxiang Chen, Jigang Wen, Fast Low-Rank Matrix Approximation with Locality Sensitive Hashing for Quick Anomaly Detection, INFOCOM 2017 (CCF A, acceptance rate of 20.93%)
[11].Kun Xie, Xiaocan Li, Xin Wang, Gaogang Xie, Jigang Wen, Jiannong Cao, Dafang Zhang, Fast Tensor Factorization for Accurate Internet Anomaly Detection, IEEE/ACM Transactions on Networking, 2017,25(6):3794 - 3807 (CCF A，SCI二区)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016</title>
      <link>https://cskxie.github.io/papers/2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 21:48:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cskxie.github.io/papers/2016/</guid>
      <description>[22].KunXie, Xin Wang, Jigang Wen, Jiannong Cao, &amp;ldquo;Cooperative Routing with Relay Assignment in Multi-radio Multihop Wireless Networks&amp;rdquo;, IEEE/ACM Transactions on Networking (TON), 2016, 24(2): 859-872 (CCF A,SCI)
[23].Kun Xie, Xin Wang, Xueli Liu, Jigang Wen, Jiannong Cao, Interference-aware Cooperative Communication in Multi-radio Multi-channel Wireless Networks, IEEE Transactions on Computers, 2016, 65(5): 1528-1542 (CCF A, SCI)
[24].Kun Xie, Lele Wang, Xin Wang, Gaogang Xie, JigangWen, Guangxing Zhang, Accurate Recovery of Internet Traffic Data: A Tensor Completion Approach, Infocom 2016 (CCF A, acceptance rate of 18.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2015</title>
      <link>https://cskxie.github.io/papers/2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 21:48:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cskxie.github.io/papers/2015/</guid>
      <description>[38].Kun Xie, Lele Wang, Xin Wang, Gaogang Xie, Guangxing Zhang, DongliangXie, Jigang Wen, Sequential and Adaptive Sampling for Matrix Completion in Network Monitoring Systems, Infocom 2015 (CCF A, acceptance rate of 19%)
[39].Kun Xie, Kexin Xie, Shiming He, Daqiang Zhang, Jigang Wen, JaimeLloret, Busy Tone Based Channel Access Control for Cooperative Communication, Transactions on Emerging Telecommunications Technologies, 2015, 26(10): 1173-1188.
[40].Kun Xie, Wang Luo, Xin Wang, Lele Wang, Jigang Wen, Road Condition Gathering With Vehicular DTN, Infocom workshop on SmartCity 2015</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2014</title>
      <link>https://cskxie.github.io/papers/2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 21:48:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cskxie.github.io/papers/2014/</guid>
      <description>[54].Kun Xie, Lele Wang, Xin Wang, Jigang Wen, Gaogang Xie, Learning from the Past: Intelligent On-Line Weather Monitoring based on Matrix Completion, ICDCS 2014 (CCF B, acceptance rate of 13%)
[55].Kun Xie, Ling Wang, Xueli Liu, Jigang Wen, Jiannong Cao, Cooperative Routing with Relay Assignment in Multi-radio Multi-hop Wireless Networks, IWQoS2014(CCF B, acceptance ratio of 23.8%)
[56].He Shiming, Zhang Dafang, Xie Kun, Qiao Hong, Zhang ji. Channel Aware Opportunistic Routing in Multi-radio Multi-channel Wireless Mesh Network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2013 and before</title>
      <link>https://cskxie.github.io/papers/2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 21:48:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cskxie.github.io/papers/2013/</guid>
      <description>[65].Kun Xie, Jiannong Cao, Xin Wang, Jigang Wen. Optimal ResourceAllocation for Reliable and Energy Efficient Cooperative Communications. IEEE Transactions on Wireless Communications, 2013,12(10),4994-5007 (SCI二区, CCF B类)
[66].Kun Xie, Jiannong Cao, Jigang Wen. Optimal Relay Assignment and Power Allocation for Cooperative Communications. Journal of Computer Science andTechnology,2013, 28(2): 343-356 (SCI,CCF B类)
[67].Kun Xie, Yuqin Ji, Jigang Wen, Shiming He. Stackelberg Game Based Pricing Mechanism for QoS Aware Resource Allocation in Wireless Networks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>